The Git Times — Tuesday, August 25, 2026
Tiny Zig Proxy Masks Telegram Traffic as HTTPS to Evade Censors
v1.13.0 adds Hysteria2 egress support and fixes live-server bugs undetected by CI
AI: TensorFlow 2.21 drops Python 3.9 support and decouples TensorBoard
Robotics: Rerun 0.36.2 fixes external link bugs in multimodal data viewer
Cyber: Agent-less Go vulnerability scanner vuls adds multi-OS support in latest release
Systems: x64dbg-MCP Server Brings Agentic Debugging to Reverse Engineering Workflows
DIY: HAL Adds Precise Simulation Controls for FPGA Netlist Debugging
GameDev: Rust GUI Library Egui Adds Drag Detection Fix in Latest Release
"The daily paper for people who build."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com